Hi, I'm Kerri and I'm at Zebra in Berkeley.
I'm here to talk about treating a tongue piercing infection.
Tongue piercing infections are rare.
Tongue piercings are the fastest-healing piercing in your body because it's the most important to your body.
When they do get infected, it's bad.
Really bad.
The signs of a tongue infection is extreme discoloration and coating of the tongue, sometimes in a yellow or greenish color.
You will also see pus coming out of the entry and exit holes of the tongue.
Tongue piercings are very dangerous when they do get infected, and so I'm not even going to give any other option except for to go see a doctor.
If you're not sure if your piercing is infected or not, please visit your local professional body piercer and they will be able to tell you if it is truly infected or just going through the normal healing process.